Tulsa, OK 74105

918-814-7325

brett.p.davis101@gmail.com

menacingmanatee.github.io/ Brett-Davis

linkedin.com/in/brett-p-davis

# Languages

C#	****
Unity	****
С	<b>★★★★</b> ☆
Python	***
SQL	***
HTML	***
CSS	***
Javascript	***

#### **Skills**

- Interpersonal and written communication
- Debugging
- Multitasking
- Teamwork
- Time management
- Task prioritization

### Education

Holberton School (Atlas School) Jan. 2020 - Sept. 2021

Tulsa, OK

Diploma in Computer Science and Full Stack Web Development Specialization in AR/VR

Development

- 20-month hands-on, peer learning program with a project-based curriculum
- Focus in web development technologies, including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, as well as backend technologies such as SQL, Python, and C

# Brett Davis VR Software Developer

#### **Professional Summary**

Multifaceted Software Developer well-versed in every aspect of producing VR games and experiences. Stays on top of demands in fast-paced environments by prioritizing based on impact versus time to complete. Knowledgeable about Unity development, game design, and debugging.

#### **Related Experience**

Lead Software Developer | Aaru Entertainment | Sept. 2021 - Dec. 2024 Remote (Tulsa OK, Bixby OK)

- Created and maintained code bases for training simulators used for police and firefighters
- Developed 'Sassin, a VR freerunning, parkour, and assassination game from initial concept through release using .NET C#, SQL, and Unity technologies
- Tested game builds to ensure functionality, stability, and adherence to design specifications
- Optimized game performance by identifying and addressing bottlenecks in code and rendering processes
- Balanced multiple VR projects simultaneously, maintaining high quality while meeting strict deadlines
- Created initial company website using frontend and backend technologies, including HTML5, CSS, and Javascript
- Developed and maintained multiple internal tools using various technologies, including SQL, Batch, and Python

## Other Experience

ADC Attendant | Goodwill Industries | July 2018 - Jan. 2022 Tulsa County, OK

Campaign Manager | Indigo Promotions | Jan 2018 - July 2018 Tulsa, OK

Cake Decorator | Reasors | July 2015 - Dec 2017 Tulsa, OK

#### **Projects**

Sassin Released Nov 2024

https://store.steampowered.com/app/2582450/Sassin/

- Developed a multiplayer VR game using C# and Unity that blends effortless freerunning and parkour with a predator vs prey style of gameplay
- Created a complex stabbing system that allows the user to use their dagger as a tool to further enhance mobility

#### **VR Training Simulators**

Police Training Simulator:

- Developed using C# and Unity through collaboration with Bixby Police.
- Scenarios available for traffic stops and active shooter training.

Firefighter Training Simulator:

- Developed using C# and Unity through collaboration with Bixby Fire Department
- Search and rescue and first-aid scenarios available in a realistic house fire situation